Hello.
So here we will be talking about the different car types in the NFC field.
The scepter, in fact provides an overview of variety of cards in Id1 format.
Because many applications have a special interest in combining several functions, especially when the
cards used in an existing system, such as magnetic stripe cards.
So these cards are intended to be replaced by smart cards.
In such cases, it's usually not possible to replace the existing infrastructure by a new technology
overnight.
The solution to this problem usually consists of issuing cards with magnetic stripes, as well as chips
for used during a transition period.
Such cards can be used with both types of terminals old and new.
For example, naturally, new functions that are only possible with a chip cannot be used with a terminal
that only supports magnetic stripe cards.
Similar considerations apply to the transition from contact smart cards to contactless smart cards.
In many cases, the infrastructure must be able to support both types of cards during an extended transition
period.
Foreign factors other than id1 have now became established.
In some applications where compatibility with magnetic stripe cards is not necessary.
SIM cards in ID 000 format are one example.
Naturally, the information regarding electrical properties and functions also applies to these other
form factors.
So first let's talk about embossed cards.
For example, we see this type of cards in the banking cards on post cards, meaning this information
that we can see the number of the cards, the the value, the expiration date example.
Some things like this.
So embossing is the oldest technique for adding machine readable features to identification cards.
The embossed characters on the card can be transferred to paper using simple, inexpensive devices,
and they can easily be read visually, visually by humans.
Here is a picture showing the two embossed regions.
Region one.
For example, this one is intended for the identification number, so it's 19 characters, while region
two is intended for the name and address, four lines of 27 characters each.
The simplicity of this technique has made worldwide use of credit cards possible even in developing
countries.
So utilization of this technology requires neither electrical power or a connection to a telephone network.
So the second type of cards is the magnetic stripe cards.
The essential disadvantage of embossed cards is that their use creates a lot of paper receipts, which
are expensive to handle and process.
One remedy to this problem is to digitally encode the card data on a magnetic stripe located on the
back of the card.
The magnetic stripe is read by pulling it across a read head, either manually or automatically.
After this, the read data can be used in the system without any human intervention.
One of the properties of magnetic stripes are the strength of the magnetic field, necessary to modify
the data on the magnetic stripe.
The magnetic stripe may have up to three tracks, as illustrated in the first picture.
Tracks one and two are specified to be read only tracks, while track 3rd May also be written to.
For the first picture, which present the magnetic stripe location on an ID one card, the data region
of the magnetic stripe is intentionally not extended to the edges of the card, since the use of hand
operated card readers causes rapid wear at the ends of the stripe.
Although the storage capacity of the magnetic stripe is fairly small, around 1000 bits, it's more
than sufficient for storing the information contained in the embossing.
Additional data can be read and written on tracks three, such as the most recent transaction data in
the case of a credit card.
The track locations are shown in the second picture.
The main drawback of magnetic stripe technology is that the stored data can be altered very easily.
Manipulating embossed characters requires at least a certain amount of manual dexterity, and such manipulations
can readily can readily be detected by a trained eye.
By contrast, the data recorded on the magnetic stripe can easily be altered using a standard read or
write device, and is difficult to prove such changes afterward.
So what about the smart cards?
So smart cards are the latest innovation in the family of identification cards in id1 format.
Their characteristic feature is an integrated circuit embedded in the card body, which has components
for transmitting, storing, and processing data.
The data can be transmitted by contacts on the surface of the card, or by an electromagnetic field,
without using contacts.
Smart cards offer several advantages compared with magnetic stripe cards.
For example, the maximum storage capacity capacity of a smart card is many times greater than, uh,
than the one of a magnetic stripe card.
Chips with memory capacities in the megabyte range are now available, and the maximum capacity increases
with each new chip generations.
However, one of the most important advantages of smart cards is that their stored data can be protected
against unauthorized access and manipulation.
The data can only be accessed via a serial interface that is controlled by the operating system or security
logic, which means that confidential data can be stored in the card in a manner that prevents it from
ever being read from outside the card.
So what about contactless memory cards?
So contactless memory cards have have come into widespread use in recent years.
Standard cards compliant with ISO 14,443 have an operating range of up to ten centimetres.
The usable memory capacity ranges from several hundred bytes to a few kilobytes.
The memory can be partitioned into several sectors that are independently protected against unauthorized
reading, writing, and erasing.
This enables a single card to support several different applications.
Each card in fact has a unique serial number stored in Rome, as well as authentication logic using
a challenge response method.
A typical architecture for contactless memory cards is shown in the first picture.
Typical applications for contactless memory cards are contactless ticketing in local transport systems
and identification cards for companies, official bodies or universities.
Electronic purse functionality, such as for company cafeteria or university cafeteria, for example,
can also be implemented on such cards.
Contactless technology compliant with ISO 4443 is also used extensively, now in radio frequency identification
tags.
The first picture presents a typical architecture of a memory card with security logic and contactless
interface.
The second picture here presents typical architecture of a contact processor card with a co-processor
and mask programmed role.
So what's the difference between contact and contactless smart cards?
So as we said, contact smart card are identified by a gold or silver chip that is visible on the card
body, much like a computer.
This chip contains its own operating system profile and card file structure that varies from application
to application.
These cards are named contact due to the fact that they physically need to be.
They physically need to be inserted into a card reader to make contact with the mechanism for the most
secure mode or encrypted communication.
In fact, the contact smart card is basically a plastic card which can be read only when it's brought
into contact with the card reader.
It derives its power from the card reader.
It typically has a contact area of approximately one centimeter square with several gold plated contact
pads.
The contact pads provide electrical connectivity to the reader.
Communication protocols for contact smart cards are defined in ISO 7816 three specification.
By the way, when we talk about contact smart cards, we refer always to the ISO 7816 standard.
However, when we talk about contactless smart cards, we refer to the ISO 14,443 standard.
And for your information, as you may know, one card can be contact and contactless at the same time.
For example, our banking card today we can pay with contact or contactless mode for the contactless,
there is always a limit of payment of amount.
So regarding contactless smart card, in fact, contactless smart cards differ from contact because
the chip is not visible on the card.
Instead, the chip and chip's antenna are embedded within the card body.
The card is waved over an RFID reader instead of inserted like a contact card.
When the contactless card passes through the specifically tuned RFID field, the antenna powers up the
chip and relays the chip's information to the application.
As the name suggests, contactless smart cards can be read without bringing the card in contact with
the reader.
The card communicates with the reader through RFID induction technology, which also powers the card.
The RFID technology used in this case works over a short range less than four inches.
As such, the card should be held near to the reader.
The card includes an embedded secure microcontroller or equivalent intelligence, internal memory,
and a small antenna for communicating with the reader.
Finally, when the card is brought into the electromagnetic field of the reader, the chip in the card
is powered on, as we have seen earlier.
Once the chip is powered on, a wireless communication protocol is initiated and established between
the card and the reader for data transfer.
So as I said before, and I try to repeat this every time the card, the contactless card doesn't communicate
without a magnetic field from the reader.
So once we put the card into the field, the contactless cards start communicating.
So start sending its answers to the comments from the reader.